Excuse me, sir. Question for you.
How did you get rich?
>> mean?
>> How did you get rich? I have a channel
with 24 million followers. I go all over
the world interviewing the richest
people. How did you get rich?
>> Give me a dollar and I'll tell you.
>> A dollar?
>> Yeah.
>> I have a hundred.
>> I'll take a hundred.
>> You want a hundred?
>> You want a secret? You're going to pay
for it.
>> How did you get rich, then? What did you
do?
>> Have you played Grand Theft Auto?
>> GTA?
>> Yes.
>> Like GTA V?
>> You like it?
>> Yes.
>> Okay, good.
>> Is that your company?
>> That's one of our games, yes.
>> is your company today?
>> It's big. It's got about a 40 billion
dollar market cap.
>> it a computer business?
>> A computer business.
>> Did you have your own
>> company?
>> Yes.
>> So, what was the most amount of money
you made in a single year?
>> 650 million.
>> Are you serious?
>> I make very expensive and sell them
through the finest galleries all over
the world.
>> the most amount of money you made in a
single day?
>> I made a million dollars in a day
before.
>> Do you
>> I do, actually.
>> You believe in God?
>> Absolutely.
>> Who is your God?
>> I don't know.
>> Who is your God, my man?
>> I believe in the source. I believe in
the universe.
>> Uh
>> I got to think about this.
>> Unquestionably. [music]
And I'm not sure you'd call that
believing in God, but I do have a
spiritual life.
>> People say my God is better than your
God, so [music] I don't go in that
direction.
>> Was there ever a point in time in your
life where you were part of a religion
or
>> part of anything like that? Ready?
>> You ready? You ready?
>> New York City is the richest city in the
entire world, and I'm not kidding.
There's more millionaires and
billionaires [music] that live here than
any other city on Earth. But today, I'm
not just asking them how they got rich.
I'm asking them something much deeper.
Do they believe in God? If you've
achieved everything that money can buy,
what do you actually believe in? This
video is brought to you by Shopify.
[music] That being said, let's get this
video on the way.
Excuse me, sir. How old were you when
you became a millionaire?
>> I'm not a millionaire.
>> No, real quick, sir. I got a channel I I
got 23 million followers. I've
interviewed 56 billionaires. Hey, how
Wait, real quick, real quick.
Nice to meet you, sir. 23 million
followers, 56 million.
All right, my man. Have a good one.
Excuse me, sir. Question for you. How
old were you when you became a
millionaire? Real quick, sir. I got a
channel with 23 million.
Excuse me, sir. Sir.
How Real quick, sir? I got to turn it
with 20
>> I love your stuff. I know you.
>> Could I get 30 seconds? It'll be worth
it, man.
All right, man. All right, brother.
Excuse me, sir. How old were you when
you became a millionaire?
I interview millionaires and
billionaires to help the younger
generation. Just 30 seconds with you?
>> Welcome.
>> All right, man. Excuse me, sir. Sir, how
did you get rich?
>> I've seen you on uh
>> How did you get rich, man?
>> How did you get rich?
>> Come on.
>> You do it.
>> Hey, real quick, man. Real quick, can we
do it?
>> How do you get rich?
>> Hey, I'm just asking millionaires and
billionaires out in New York City
whether or not they believe in God.
>> We're just private.
>> Wow, you're good. I believe
>> I watched you on
>> Do you believe in God? Yes or no?
>> Yes, I do.
>> How did you know God was real? Who is
your God?
Hey, look. As you can see, man, these
millionaires and billionaires aren't
stopping for anything. He's seen the
channel before, you guys. But look, I
didn't come out to New York City for
nothing, man. I'm going to find the
wealthiest people, the richest people
out in New York City. I'm going to stop
them, figure out how they got rich,
built their milli-dollar, billion-dollar
companies, and whether or not they
believe in God, and who is their God.
So, let's go see who we can find.
>> What's up?
>> I follow your videos, man.
>> I appreciate that.
>> spectacular.
>> You look more buff than normal, huh?
>> You look buff, man.
>> No, you're buff, right?
>> you get rich, though?
>> Do I look rich to you?
>> You look rich, man. Are you?
>> What do you think?
>> I think so.
>> so? Look at the eyes.
>> The eyes don't lie, man.
>> You think I am?
>> I think so. What do you do?
>> I work in the art business.
>> The art business?
>> Yes.
>> Are you a dealer?
>> No, I make very expensive artworks and
sell them through the finest galleries
all over the world.
>> So, what's the most amount of money you
made in a single day?
>> I made a million dollars in a day
before.
>> You did that?
>> I've sold I've sold editions of certain
artworks. Galleries bought the entire
edition, which is a million dollars. For
every image I make, it's a million
dollars.
>> What was the secret to making a million
dollars in a day? I mean, that's fast.
>> Not thinking about the money. Thinking
about the work. You got to believe it to
see it in a world that needs to see it
to believe it.
>> Say that again.
>> That again. Sorry. You need to believe
it to see it in a world that so often
needs to see it to believe it.
>> If you love to win
>> you'll always make money.
>> What age did you make your first
million?
>> Early 30s.
>> So, you've been a millionaire for a
while now.
>> I never I never think that way. I never
think I'm a millionaire. I think I've
been winning for a while.
>> ever get comfortable?
>> I'm always comfortably uncomfortable.
>> What's that mean?
>> I'm very comfortable being
uncomfortable.
>> When you're an entrepreneur, you're
never comfortable. You know why? Because
no success nor failure is ever final. Do
you believe in God?
>> I believe in the source. I believe in
the universe. I really feel like when
you look up at the sky, you can feel
something cuz it's always moving. It's
never the same.
>> Not a particular religion though?
>> No. No.
>> You know what? You know, I'm a big
believer, man. I'm a big Christian. You
know why? And I always like to talk
about this, man. Creation like us has to
have a designer. I'm a firm believer,
man. There's got to be a higher power
bigger than us that made us.
>> in the universe, but I'm not I'm not
really into I don't call it anything
other than source and the universe. And
the And the universe has always been my
guide. It's always been my guide.
>> Was there ever a point in time in your
life where you were part of a religion
or part of anything like that? Or you
just kind of it wasn't for you, maybe?
>> I love everybody, man. I think religion
gets in the way cuz I think people say
my God is better than your God. So, I
don't go in that direction. I just love
everybody. I don't care what you look
like. I care more about how you feel
than what you look like.
>> 100%.
>> Are you a good salesman? You tell me.
>> Are you a good salesman? Now, be honest.
This is the show to talk your
>> I'm I I'm a fantastic salesperson.
>> you learn about price? One of my
favorite things is that price is only an
issue if value is absent.
>> Give me a This is being filmed right
now. By the way, how great is the Is one
of your favorite things to do?
>> Fantastic. No, I love That's why we're
here for so long. If I didn't like you,
we we wouldn't be
>> Exactly. Exactly.
>> What did you learn about price?
>> You ready? You ready? You ready?
>> Give me your Come on.
>> The higher the price, the easier is to
sell the art.
>> I don't know.
>> It's crazy. It's much easier to sell a
piece of art for more than $25,000 than
it is for less than 10.
>> It's way easier to
>> It's not It's not easy, but people feel
like it's more special sometimes when
it's at that price point and there's
very little availability.
>> Price is only an issue when value is
absent.
>> How old are you now?
>> How old do you think?
>> 41.
>> 56 in August.
>> No, you're not.
>> 56 years old coming up soon. In August
soon. If me and you died tomorrow, you
had one more message to leave with the
younger generation, what would that be?
>> It's always two words.
>> Be yourself.
>> Because everyone else is taken.
>> You have amazing advice, sir.
>> No, YOU'RE THE MAN.
>> WOO!
>> HEY, I I like to connect with all the
millionaires and billionaires I
interview. Could I get your contact?
>> Yeah.
>> Guys, those are always the best
interviews right there. My guy comes up
to me, was a fan of the channel, that
man made a million dollars in a day in
the art business, man. It does not get
any better than that. You know he was a
good salesman, but he just gave an
incredible interview talking about being
authentic being one of his superpowers
in the business world. Nonetheless, I
asked him if he believed in God, didn't
necessarily give us anything specific
right there, said it was maybe part of
the universe for him, but he attributed
that as part to his success. Great
interview. We got to go find this
actually out here. Go get this
interview, guys. Come on.
Excuse me, sir. Question for you. How
did you get rich? How did you get rich?
I have a channel with 24 million
followers. I go all over the world
interviewing the richest people. How did
you get rich?
>> Give me a dollar and I'll tell you.
>> A dollar?
>> Yeah.
>> I have a hundred.
>> I'll take a hundred.
>> You want a hundred?
>> I'll take a hundred. You want a secret,
huh? You're going to pay for it.
All right. Here we go.
>> How did you get rich?
>> I sold a food company.
>> A food company?
>> Yep.
>> For how much money?
>> One and a half billion dollars.
>> No you did not.
>> I did.
>> What type of company was it?
>> We shipped fresh meals directly to your
house. We were the third fastest growing
food company ever.
>> No you were not.
>> Yeah. Went to zero to 550 million in
sales in a little over five years.
>> Can I interview for a minute? I go all
over the world interviewing 60
billionaires around the world.
>> You paid for it. Let's let's do it.
>> You built one of the biggest food
companies in the world. 1.5 billion
dollars. You think about the richest
people you know in your network. What's
that one trait they all have in common?
What do the most successful people have
in common?
>> They work harder than everyone else. At
the end of the day there's no there's no
shortcut. You got to be willing to put
in the work. I'm not the smartest. I'm
not the best looking, but I'm the
hardest working. I'll put in more work
than anyone else and that over time
compounds.
>> work hard, but you can work hard and
work at a fast food restaurant. Give me
something else. What is it?
>> You got to work hard for yourself. If
you want to create wealth, you have to
start your own thing. You can't work
hard for someone else. Not that that
can't ultimately get you a good salary,
but if you really want to create wealth,
you got to do your own thing.
>> Did you have rich parents? Did you come
from money?
>> I did not. I had $15 in my bank account
when I started the business. I was 35
when I started it.
>> You had $15 at 35 years old?
>> I had $15. I'd lost I'd started a
company before that. It went bankrupt. I
came off that though with tenacity,
passion. I had a million dollars in debt
that I had to pay off. So nothing like
that sense of urgency. I had three years
to pay it off. So I had a great idea.
We'd already had some product market fit
and I said, well, we got to go. So I I'm
a big fan of like, you know, your back's
against the wall, you make it happen.
>> Take the glasses off. I got to see the
eyes.
>> There we go.
>> I want your face to see that way people
can see your face. What's your name?
>> Michael Weistrach.
>> I want you to talk to the broke Michael.
I want you to talk to the broke you at
35 years old with $15 to your name. Talk
to the people watching right now. What's
that first actionable step they can take
to get rich in today's world?
>> The key is you got to stop wishing and
you got to decide. So, the difference is
wishing is I wish I was a founder. I
wish I started something. I wish I was
self-employed. Decision is I am as
founder. I am going to be self-employed
and do an action. Do something right
now. If you're watching this, get off
Instagram, get off YouTube, and go do
something that is going to change your
life.
>> Did you have any marketing or branding
tactics that helped you build a
billion-dollar company? What is your
number one marketing or branding tactic
for anybody starting a business?
>> You have to be relentlessly data-focused
every single day. Every day, there's a
new thing. We were the absolute best at
meta marketing. No one beat us. We built
a $550 million company in 5 years,
almost 99% on meta because we were the
absolute best.
>> Running ads?
>> Running ads. TikTok to Instagram. You
got to understand these things. You got
to understand the data. You can measure
relentlessly. Know what's working. Know
exactly what's performing. Be
intellectually honest with yourself.
Don't be afraid to move quickly. Don't
be afraid to test and fail.
>> Are you a good salesman?
>> I have gotten better over the years.
>> have a sales and negotiation tactic for
anybody in business? Like, what is the
number one sales and negotiation advice
that turned you into a billion-dollar
founder?
>> Ask questions. Ask questions. Don't I
think people think sales is about
talking. It's about asking, really
listening to what people need, and then
seeing if you're if you can provide a
solution for that.
>> have investors in your company?
>> Had a ton of investors. Started with
100% ownership, ended of it. Sold the
business for 1.5 billion, owned 10% of
it. So, you can do the math there. At
the end of the day, if I didn't sell
that 90% and get all the people I got
around, including employees, including
thing, there's no 1.5 billion exit.
>> there a risk taking investors in because
now you're giving up some control, some
decision-making to other people? Is
there a risk with taking on investors?
>> the hubris in there is that I have all
the right answers. I think I'm I'm
intellectually honest with myself to be
like, I can get smarter people who've
done things and I can listen to them.
They will respect me and they will
acknowledge that I bring some stuff to
the table, but we're going to find the
right balance. To me, it's no different
than, you know, whatever sport you play,
you get a coach. The reason you bring
that coach on is you want to listen to
him. You don't want to argue with him
and tell him, "No, no, I'm right." It's
like you want the coach there for you.
>> a food company, right? What did you
sell?
>> prepared meals we shipped to your house.
>> So, did you have like an online store
where people would buy from you?
>> 100% online. It is now shut, but you
would go to freshly.com and buy it and
it would be shipped to your house that
day or the next day and it would show up
at your house and all you had to do
>> cheat meal. And what platform did you
use to build your stores?
>> built our own. Unfortunately, we were
before Shopify. If I was doing it today,
I would 100% do it on Shopify. It's a
rinse and repeat. Like when we had to
start it, Shopify was a very beginning
company. It didn't have all the things
that we needed around recurring revenue.
Now you can plug and play. That's the
best platform if you're doing e-commerce
at least early because everyone's
building on it, too. If we didn't have
to build it, we spent close to 40
million building our own platform. I
would have gladly taken that 40 million
and invested in other ways.
>> And you would have used Shopify.
>> I would have used Shopify.
>> 46 years old today.
>> Yes.
>> If me and you die tomorrow and you can
leave one more message with the younger
generation, what would that be?
>> If you are hiking only cuz you want to
get to the peak, don't hike. You got to
enjoy the entire journey cuz when you
get to the peak, it's never as good as
you think it is. And I'd say when you
when you sell your business, you get
that wire, it feels great for a day and
then guess what? You wake up and and
you're back to all the problems, all
those things and it didn't solve
everything that you thought it was going
to solve. So, you really have to enjoy
that journey. You have to enjoy going up
the mountain, down the mountain. And so,
for me as I always tell founders is like
if you don't like the journey, don't do
it.
>> believe in God?
>> I do.
>> your God?
>> I'm a Christian. I'm a Catholic. I grew
up in Catholic church.
>> can we tell them that Jesus is king?
>> Yeah, we can. I think religion's highly
personal. Whatever religion, they all
follow on the same foundation. Be good
to people, follow that golden rule and
work your ass off.
>> Can I tell you something? Yeah. You got
amazing advice, my friend.
>> I appreciate it, my man.
>> for your time and I like I connect with
all the billionaires that I interview.
Could I get your contact?
>> Let's give you that 100 that 100 back.
This is a fun day.
>> you for the conversation. Come on, man.
Can I get your contact?
>> You can of course you can.
>> Awesome.
>> Guys, we just interviewed an
entrepreneur out here in New York City
that sold one of the fastest growing
food companies for $1.5 billion. And one
thing he told me that absolutely blew my
mind was when I asked him, "What store
did you use to sell your products?" He
said [music] he spent millions of
dollars building his own custom store.
But if he were starting over today, he
said without a doubt, he'd be using
Shopify. Think about that. A guy who
sold his company for over a billion
dollars is telling you this is the
greatest time in history to be an
entrepreneur. But it's thanks to tools
and platforms like Shopify making it
easier to start a business than it ever
has been before. Shopify is the place
where you can turn your idea into a real
business, a real store overnight. You
can build your store, accept payments,
manage orders, and do everything all in
one place. But what makes Shopify so
powerful today is how much AI has
changed everything. With Shopify's new
AI store builder, Sidekick, it's like
having an AI co-founder at your
business. You can literally describe
your business idea, build your store,
create product descriptions, and get
help launching your store faster than
ever before. So if you've been sitting
on an idea, stop waiting wasting more
time. Go down right now, click the link
in the description of this video, or go
to shopify.com/sohk
and turn that idea into a real business.
Now that being said, let's get back to
the video. Sir,
how did you get rich?
>> How did I get rich?
>> I'm meeting you.
>> No, how did you get rich, man? Tell me.
>> I'm not rich.
>> What line of business are you in? I got
to get you on the podcast.
>> I'm retired. I don't know who you are.
I've seen you before.
>> What do you do?
>> I'm on social security.
>> So, yeah?
Did you ever own a business?
>> in a computer business.
>> A computer business? And what were you
doing exactly?
>> Selling computers back in the '80s.
>> Did you have your own company?
>> Yeah, National Data Products.
>> Actually?
>> Yeah.
>> Did you come from a family of
entrepreneurs? Did you grow up You said
you don't have rich parents.
>> Nope, my dad died when I was 12 years
old.
>> You close with your mom?
>> The best.
>> What did your mom teach you about life?
>> No bird flies so high that they don't
come down for water. Everybody's the
same. Everybody's got an opportunity.
>> How old are you today?
>> 67.
>> How big was your biggest company?
>> 650 million.
>> Are you serious? So so what was the most
amount of money you made in a single
year?
>> Oh god, 600 million.
>> Are you serious, man? As a multiple
nine-figure entrepreneur, what's the
best financial advice you would give to
the younger generation?
>> Don't ever give up. Everybody can
succeed in this country.
>> have people that doubted you at all?
>> Everybody does. Everybody thinks that
you were given stuff in your life.
Nobody understands the hard work that
went into doing that. You know, nobody
knows the hours, the years that you put
into it and then all of a sudden they
go, "Oh, they were they inherited it."
Which is not true.
>> You weren't given anything. Nothing.
Nothing. We put my mother's house up as
collateral for a loan in 1979.
>> Are you serious?
>> Yeah. We couldn't fail. My mother would
be out of her house. So, it has to work
or it has to work. You have no choice.
>> I'm going to challenge you then. In
these 67 years of life, what was the
greatest piece of advice you ever
received throughout your career? Work
hard, play hard.
>> Do you believe in God?
>> Absolutely.
>> Who is your God? Who is your God, my
man? Who's your God?
>> Jesus Christ.
>> Hey, you're not afraid to say it, man.
Jesus is king.
>> That's it, man.
>> At the end of the day, that's $650
billion. The only thing that matters is
that relationship we have with God, my
man.
>> You got it, my man.
>> You're an amazing advice, sir.
>> Thank you very
>> Hey, I I I I I connect with all the
millionaires and billionaires I
interview. Could I get your contact?
>> you forever.
>> Hey, wait. My son saw you earlier, he
said.
>> get your contact? Is that cool?
>> Sure.
>> Thank you, my man.
>> Real quick, why are you putting that in
here?
>> I wanted to ask this last one. Before
you became wealthy
Real quick, real quick. Before you
became wealthy, how did you network and
build relationships with the right
people? I want you to think about that.
Because you have to know the right
people in business, but if you don't
have like great credibility or you don't
come from money or that name, how did
you build relationships?
>> there's only I tell my kids there's only
two things in life that you control.
It's your credit and your reputation.
Everything else somebody else can ruin.
You can only ruin your credit and your
reputation.
>> Hey, that's gay right there, man. Hey,
real quick, real quick. And what
>> You wouldn't come up to this guy
>> [laughter]
>> What do the wealthiest people do with
their money differently from everybody
else?
>> I don't know. I'm done.
>> All right, my man. Have a good one. Hey,
$650 million, man. That man was not
playing at all. He was dropping solid
after solid in that interview. And we
found another believer, man. We found a
believer right there, man, in Jesus
Christ, man. We got him to say his name.
Great interview with a probably a
billionaire right there, man. He just
gave us an incredible one. We got to go
get this next one, you guys. Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir. Sir. How did you get rich?
>> What makes you think I'm rich?
>> You look like money, man. I interview
billionaires all the
>> I look like everyone else on the street.
I'm just wearing a blue suit.
>> How did you get rich, then? What did you
do?
>> Have you played Grand Theft Auto?
>> GTA?
>> Yes.
>> Like GTA V?
>> You like it?
>> Yes.
>> Okay, good.
>> Is that your company?
>> That's one of our games, yes. It's our
biggest game.
>> copies have you sold?
>> 230 million.
>> What company?
>> Take-Two Interactive.
>> How big is your company today?
>> It's big. It's got about a $40 billion
market cap.
>> all over the world doing millionaires
and billionaires. Can I get one with you
with you for the channel real quick?
>> Sure.
>> Is that cool?
>> Yeah.
>> Awesome. When is GTA 6 coming out, man?
The people
>> November 19th.
>> How did it take so long?
>> at Rockstar really does seek to do
something that's never been done before.
That's really hard and it takes a long
time.
>> How long have you been in that business
for?
>> A long time. Almost 20 years.
>> 20 years. When you approach business, do
you have a very long-term view?
>> everyone's looking for an overnight
success. My experience is the only
overnight successes are someone else's.
Everything worth doing is hard and takes
a long time. I took over Take-Two in
2007. It was at least 5 years before we
began to have real success. And I've
been at it for 19 years and I'm still at
it.
>> What was the most amount of money you
made in a single year?
>> In the year that just ended, we did $6.7
billion. Next March, we'll be over $8
billion.
>> Congratulations.
>> Oh, it's congratulations to the team,
not to me.
>> go to college?
>> Yes.
>> Where'd you go to school?
>> Harvard for uh law school and business
school.
>> But I'm going to challenge you. I want
you to give me one lesson about business
right here that is not taught in a
Harvard Business School.
>> Work hard, listen, never compromise your
integrity. It's the only thing you have.
>> have to keep your word in business is
what you're saying?
>> Unquestionably.
>> Have there ever been a time where maybe
you didn't or somebody else kind of
around you didn't and it kind of messed
up the company?
>> I have flaws. There was a time I one
time in particular where I acted in a
way that wasn't consistent with my views
about integrity in business. It hurt me
really badly and I learned a powerful
lesson. Never do that.
>> How do you take
>> How old am I?
>> Yeah.
>> 68.
>> You're not 68.
>> I am very much 68.
>> Would you say that you've made it yet?
>> I think it's important to take some
pride in the things that you've done
that have worked out. Have I done great
things? In my opinion, no, not really.
Have I pursued my passion and am I proud
of the work I did? Most of the time,
yes.
>> How many employees do you have?
>> 20,000.
>> 20,000 employees. What's your best
>> Colleagues.
>> Why not call them employees?
>> Why not?
>> Because I'm just another colleague.
>> had somebody correct me like that
before. What's your best leadership
advice to anybody running a business
today?
>> to have a mission that is
straightforward and understandable,
ambitious but achievable. You need to
state your strategy, preferably in three
words. You need to state your culture
and you need to live by it. You need to
believe it. It needs to be honest.
>> That's a master class right there. Do
you believe in God?
>> I have a spiritual life and I'm not sure
you'd call that believing in God, but I
do have a spiritual life.
>> Has that helped you out at all having
having something Talk to me about that
if you can. Like is it just kind of like
faith in a higher power or just kind of
the universe per se?
>> a belief that I'm just able to control
and be responsible for what's within my
wingspan and everything else is outside
of me. I can control my desires, my
actions, my goals, my plans. I can't
control the outcomes. The outcomes are
out of my control.
>> 68 years old today, if me and you die
tomorrow and you had one more message to
leave with the younger generation, what
would that be?
>> Think about what you truly want in life,
truly want, professionally and
personally. Not what someone wants for
you, but what you want and then go for
it.
>> Do you think people should chase their
passion or is that often not great
advice?
>> I think it's terrible advice half the
time. People should chase the
intersection of what they're good at and
what they like to do. With emphasis on
what you're good at. Everyone's good at
something. Do that thing. The world will
probably open up to you.
>> You have amazing advice, sir.
Thank you so much for your time, my
friend. And I'd like to connect with all
the millionaires and billionaires that I
interview. Can I get your contact?
>> Of course.
>> Guys, that's a wrap on today's video. I
need you to stop right now. Like and
subscribe for amazing content coming
every single week to the School of Hard
Knocks, man. But I want to go a step
further. I want to give you direct
access to every single one of the
eight-figure, nine-figure, and
billionaire entrepreneurs that I
interview on this channel. Every week I
host live Zoom calls with the
millionaires and billionaires I
interview where you can ask your
questions directly to them. Inside of my
private entrepreneur community, the
School of Mentors. If you want access,
go down right now to the link in the
description of this video to join. And I
can't wait to see you on the inside.
That being said, we'll see you in the
next video.